Hi.
Alright we're just going to chop up one small onion to add to this dish.
Alright we're just going to cut off both sides of our small onion like so.
And want to just score the onion and pull away the outer shell and begin to chop it up.
Alright, what I like to do is just cut the onion in half, put the flat sides down.
Slice the onion, going with the lines of the onion one way.
Straight down.
Turn it and just start to chop away.
Cut nice little chunks.
Again don't worry if it's not the desired consistency.
Cause what I'll do with that is again do our same chopping motion.
Chop all this onion down fine.
Alright, just when you take your onions to the side, make sure you don't put them in your bowl.
Keep them off to the side, cause we're actually going to saute our onion.
And we're going to chop now our green scallion.
And we're going to add that with our onion and we're going to actually simmer, simmer, saute both of them together.
So make sure you keep them on the side and don't put them in your bowl.